[{"answer": "That's not why we're going out", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend!  He'll drive there for me, and I'll drive to my friend for him. We're going to have sex when he's ready and I'm ready.  It's got to be completely perfect.  I want the right place, the right time, the right moment", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Nah, gave her the Heisman.  I'm working on something new", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Dude, it's gotta happen", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Bullshit.  From where", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Hah!  Yeah, Oz, I bet it's more like your dad works at  store", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Does it tell me how to get laid", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Ready for what", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Perhaps you should consider actually answering an ad", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " This is no imitation.  Removing the hot dog from the my friend yields a better dog.  Behold", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "He likes it", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I think I've had one", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "This, son, is your more exotic dirty magazine", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Do you know about the clitoris", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What?  No I'm not", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I wasn't making fun of you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What am I gonna do, broadcast her over the internet", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Oh", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Did you guys hook up or something", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Then what the hell are you talking about", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm not playing", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No.  I'm missing the game for you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "And I want to make things perfect for you.  You're right, my friend, we do have something good...and special", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend...  I want to have sex with you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah, we were up the whole night together.  We had one of those amazingly deep conversations, where you really feel like you get to know someone", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What else would I call it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "So...would you object if I said you're quite striking", "docId": "American-Pie.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes ma'am, I am", "qsentId": 28}]